A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources, 1992-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Agencies, 1992-2006., Extent: 19 cu. ft. (Box 5-58.)
  - Historic Resources, Department of, 2000-2006. (Box 51-54.)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Greenspring, 2003. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Oakwood Cemetery, 2002-2005. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Oatlands Historic District, 2003. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, 2002. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Shenandoah Valley Battlefields Foundation, 2001-2002. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Shenandoah Valley Battlefields Foundation, 2001-2002. (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Shenandoah Valley Battlefields Foundation, 2001-2002. (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Staunton Correctional Center (Old Western State Hospital Complex), 2002. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2000. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2000. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2001. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2001. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2001. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2002. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2002. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2002. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2002. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2002. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2002. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2003. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2003. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2004. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Tredegar National Civil War Center Foundation, 2005. (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - West Hospital, 2003-2004. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Marine Resources Commission, Virginia, 1996-2006. (Box 54-58.)
    The Virginia Marine Resources Commission (MRC) serves as steward of Virginia's marine and aquatic resources, and works to protect tidal waters. The Commission carries out current and long-term State policies effecting saltwater fisheries, handles a permit program that encompasses subaqueous habitat preservation and the protection and preservation of tidal wetlands and coastal primary sand dunes, and operates the Virginia Marine Police department which is responsible for the enforcement of commercial and recreational fishery laws, providing search and rescue operations, enforcing boating safety laws, investigating criminal activity, and providing counter-terrorism patrols.
    This subseries contains general correspondence and administrative information about the agency. Most of the files pertain to specific projects and issues, such as crab, oyster, and fisheries management, disaster relief, and the development of the Undersea Warfare Training Range by the U.S. Navy. Also included is meeting information from a variety of roundtables and commissions such as the Menhaden Management Roundtable, the Licensing Roundtable, and the Potomac River Fisheries Commission.
    - Administrative, 2001-2002. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Administrative, 2002-2003. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Administrative, 2003-2004. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Administrative, 2005-2006. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Crab Management, 2001-2003. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Crab Management, 2004-2005. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Crab Management, 2005. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Executive Agreement, 2002-2005. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Fisheries Disaster Relief, 2003. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Fisheries Disaster Relief, 2003-2004. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Fisheries Management, 2002. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Fisheries Management, 2002-2003. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Fisheries Management, 2003. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Grants, 2002. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Federal Blue Crab Disaster Funds, 2003. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box [box], Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Licensing Roundtable, 2004. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Menhaden Management Roundtable, 2004. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Mid-Atlantic Fishery Management Council, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Mid-Atlantic Fishery Management Council, 2003. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Oyster Management, 2002. (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Oyster Management, 2002. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Oyster Management, 2003-2005. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Petition (Native Virginia Oyster), 2005. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Pfiesteria, 2001-2002. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Potomac River Fisheries Commission, 2001-2002. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Potomac River Fisheries Commission, 2003-2005. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Recreational / Sport Fishing, 2002. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Royalties, 1996-1999. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Royalties, 1999-2002. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Royalties, 2002. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Royalties, 2003. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Royalties, 2003. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Royalties, 2003. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Royalties, 2003. (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Royalties, 2004. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Sea Turtles and Dolphins, 2004-2005. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Undersea Warfare Training Range (Fisheries Impact), 2005. (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Veined Rapa Whelk, 1998. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Wetlands, 2002-2003. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Wetlands, 2004-2005. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Natural History, Virginia Museum of, 2002-2006. (Box 58.)
    The Virginia Museum of Natural History (MNH) is located in Martinsville, Virginia, and is an affiliate of the Smithsonian Institution. Its goal is to interpret Virginia's natural heritage in ways that are relevant to the citizens of the Commonwealth. Through exhibits and outreach programs, the museum promotes understanding of the state's natural history and the challenges of preserving and managing natural resources.
    This subseries is comprised of mostly administrative files, specifically those that deal with a multitude of personnel problems faced by the Museum of Natural History. Some of the files also include information about the development and dedication of the new museum building, as well as changes in museum leadership.
    - Administrative, 2002. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Administrative, 2002. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Administrative, 2003. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Administrative, 2003. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Administrative, 2003. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Administrative, 2004-2006. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Administrative--Grievances, 2002. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Administrative--Grievances, 2002. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Executive Agreement, 2002-2005. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2003-2005. (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Series IV. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Constituent, 2002-2006., Extent: 10.7 cu. ft. (Box 59-89.)
  Contains constituent correspondence pertaining to all agencies and boards overseen by the Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources. Most of the letters were originally addressed to Governor Mark Warner, but were assigned to the Secretary of Natural Resources for response based on their subject matter. 2002 topics include: budget cuts affecting DGIF, concerns that the VMRC was not doing enough to protect marine resources, protest over the King William Reservoir project aimed to serve Newport News by using the Mattaponi River, support and opposition to the gun ban in VA state parks, the Interstate Waste Bill (HR 1213), as well as the $5/ton tipping fee, the severe drought and water restrictions, the building of a golf course on land in Occoneechee State Park. 2003 topics include: budget cuts, particularly those affecting Virginia state parks, Attorney General Kilgore's support for weakening the EPA Clean Air regulations, continued protest of the King William Reservoir project, concern over the Battle Creek Landfill in Page County, requests for funding to continue the Bi-State Blue Crab Committee, and requests to allow hunting on Sundays. 2004 topics include: concern about air pollution caused by power plants in the Shenandoah River Valley and National Park, the presence of noxious aquatic weeds in Lake Gaston, proposed deforestation near the Washington and Old Dominion trail in Loudoun County to make way for Dominion Virginia Power electrical lines, support and protest of a proposed conference center in Occoneechee State Park, protest over changes to the Roadless Area Conservation Rule, menhaden fishing limits, and continued concern about the King William Reservoir project. 2005 topics include: allegations of fiscal irresponsibility at the Department of Game and Inland Fisheries resulting in the resignation of its director, concern for the future of the Zirkle Mill in Forestville and plans to transport it to the Frontier Culture Museum in Staunton, hunting with dogs and issues of trespass and property rights, the Roadless Rule and the destruction of forests in Virginia, the water quality and frequent fish kills in the Shenandoah River, continued concern about menhaden fishing limits and the King William Reservoir project, and protest about the proposed "Black Bear" landfill just across the North Carolina border from Chesapeake, Virginia. More generally, constituents wrote about the need for recycling, concern for fish and animal well-being, and to inquire about various forms of pollution control.
  Constituent correspondence is arranged chronologically by year, but also by the outgoing number generated by the Governor's Office. As a result, the letters are in rough chronological order, but there may be some overlap between months, especially during the December/January time period each year. (Accessions 42294 and 42398).
  - 2002
    - #2000187 - 2000234, January. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - #2000235 - 2000258, January. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - #2000259, January. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - #2000385 - 2000398, January. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - #2000405 - 2000494, January. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - #2000496 - 2000793, January - February. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - #2000794 - 2001157, February. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - #2001234 - 2002066, February. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - #2002098 - 2002465, February. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - #2002466 - 2002577, February. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - #2002585 and 2002713, February. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - #2002711 - 2002776, February. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - #2002830 - 2003332, February. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - #2003077 - 2003173; 2003357 - 2003408, February. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - #2003394 - 2003576, February. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - #2003578 - 2003957, February. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - #2004081 - 2004439, February. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - #2004486 - 2004719, February. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - #2004736 - 2005038, February. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - #2005040 - 2005467, February. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - #2005468 - 2005612, February - March. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - #2005619 - 2005943, March. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - #2005947 - 2006602, March. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - #2006657 - 2007321, March. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - #2007704 - 2008520, March. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - #2008993 - 2009997, March. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - #2010378 - 2010882, March. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - #2010876 - 2011396, March. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - #2011471 - 2011807, March. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - #2011813 - 2012190, March. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - #2012295 - 2012323, March. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - #2012605 - 2013124, March. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - #2013126 - 2013359, March. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - #2013360 - 2013738, March. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - #2013826 - 2013979, March. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - #2014037 - 2014728, March - April. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - #2014729 - 2014888, April. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - #2014889 - 2015441, April. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - #2015442 - 2015680, April. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - #2015681 - 2015687, April. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - #2015688 - 2015920, April. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - #2016102 - 2016181, April. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - #2016190 - 2016609, April. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - #2016610 - 2016789, April. (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - #2016911 - 2017019, April. (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - #2017021 - 2017096, April. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - #2017165 - 2017390, April. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - #2017395 - 2017878, April. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - #2017925 - 2018407, April. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - #2018408 - 2018416, April. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - #2018417 - 2018488, April. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - #2018489 - 2018829, April. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - #2018830 - 2019714, April. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - #2019715 - 2019853, April. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - #2019855 - 2020419, April - May. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - #2020420 - 2020754, May. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - #2020908 - 2020998, May. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - #2021028 - 2021385, May. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - #2021401 - 2022368, May. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - #2022647 - 2023425, May. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - #2023989 - 2025874, May. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - #2023647 - 2023953, May. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - #2025879 - 2026564, May - June. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - #2026568 - 2027087, June. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - #2027116 - 2028168, June. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - #2028170 - 2028250, June. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - #2029809 - 2030279, June. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - #2030354 - 2030497, June. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - #2030586 - 2030903, June. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - #2031067 - 2031508, June. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - #2031551, June. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - #2031573 - 2031819, June. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - #2031883 - 2032234, June. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - #2032235 - 2032704, June - July. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - #2032737 - 2032739, July. (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - #2032774 - 2032936, July. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - #2032954 - 2033428, July. (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - #2033567 - 2033827, July. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - #2033850 - 2034580, July. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - #2034593 - 2034753, July. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - #2034754 - 2035011, July. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - #2035012 - 2035300, July. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - #2035407 - 2035761, July - August. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - #2035766 - 2036225, July - August. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - #2036281 - 2036743, August. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - #2036862 - 2037090, August. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - #2037147 - 2038025, August. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - #2038136 - 2038797, August. (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - #2038910 - 2038925, August. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - #2039000 - 2039812, August. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - #2040007 - 2040225, August. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - #2049637 - 2050234, August. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - #2050280 - 2050769, August - September. (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - #2050770 - 2051087, September. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - #2041450 - 2041778, September. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - #2041870 - 2042611, September. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - #2042614 - 2043127, September. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - #2043137 - 2043397, September. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - #2043439 - 2043578, September. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - #2043686 - 2043979, September. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - #2043983 - 2044150, September. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - #2044153 - 2044531, September. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - #2044599 - 2045122, September. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - #2045186 - 2047472, September. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - #2047483 - 2047795, September. (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - #2047814 - 2049095, September. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - #2049097 - 2049509, September. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - #2049581 - 2050373, September - October. (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - #2050751 - 2052461, September - October. (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - #2052480 - 2052725, October. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - #2052844 - 2053795, October. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - #2053797 - 2055071, October. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - #2055082 - 2055184, October. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - #2055317 - 2055797, October. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - #2055803 - 2056640, October. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - #2056646 - 2056903, October - November. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - #2056917 - 2057656, October - November. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - #2057786 - 2058194, October. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - #2058244 - 2058880, October. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - #2058889 - 2060408, October - November. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - #2060410 - 2061207, November. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - #2061481 - 2062896, November. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - #2062903 - 2064686, November. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - #2064747 - 2065485, November. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - #2065490 - 2065788, November. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - #2066049 - 2066763, November. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - #2066772 - 2067940, November. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - #2068010 - 2068344, November. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - #2068388 - 2068926, November. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - #2068927 - 2069242, November - December. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - #2069243 - 2069437, December. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - #2069438 - 2069712, December. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - #2069713 - 2070021, December. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - #2070040 - 2070169, December. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - #2070187 - 2070846, December. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - #2070850 - 2071061, December. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - #2071063 - 2071549, December. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - #2071561 - 2071781, December. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - #2071809 - 2072134, December. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - #2072143 - 2072562, December. (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - #2072786 - 2073325, December. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - #2073343 - 2073827, December. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - #2073888 - 2074162, December. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - #2074163 - 2074936, December. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - #2074949 - 2075242, December. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - #2075699 - 2076678, December. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - #2076757 - 2076877, December. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - #2076937 - 2078352, December. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - #2078493 - 2078954, December. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - #2078966 - 2079162, December. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - #2079166 - 2080323, December. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - 2003
    - #2080134 - 2080562, January. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - #2080574 - 2081474, January. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - #2081539 - 2081918, January. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - #2081977 - 2082601, January. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - #2082607 - 2083375, January. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - #2083525 - 2084123, January. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - #2084124 - 2084569, January. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - #2084570 - 2085341, January. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - #2085418 - 2085832, January. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - #2085913 - 2086677, January. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - #2087262 - 2088189, January. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - #2088453 - 2090370, January. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - #2090675 - 2091332, January. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - #2091373 - 2092047, January. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - #2092194 - 2092916, January. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - #2093043 - 2094156, January. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - #2094334 - 2094974, January. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - #2095555 - 2097716, January - February. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - #2097719 - 2098726, February. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - #2098727 - 2099084, February. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - #2099273 - 2101051, February. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - #2101055 - 2101829, February. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - #2102180 - 2103479, February. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - #2103585 - 2106655, February. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - #2106663 - 2107025, February. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - #2107036 - 2107377, February. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - #2107464 - 2108369, February. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - #2108476 - 2109636, February. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - #2109865 - 2110708, February. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - #2110803 - 2111838, February - March. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - #2111954 - 2113510, March. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - #2113634 - 2115620, March. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - #2116527 - 2117721, March. (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - #2117817 - 2118517, March. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - #2118601 - 2119620, March. (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - #2119946 - 2120320, March. (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - #2120326 - 2121267, March. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - #2121838 - 2122302, March. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - #2122321 - 2124631, March - April. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - #2124836 - 2125384, March - April. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - #2125385 - 2126143, March. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - #2126149 - 2126984, March. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - #2127084 - 2128330, March - April. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - #2128342 - 2130573, March - April. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - #2132338 - 2134208, April. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - #2134217 - 2135361, April. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - #2135412 - 2136592, April. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - #2136647 - 2137180, April. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - #2137676 - 2138350, April. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - #2138466 - 2138546, April. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - #2138547 - 2138933, April. (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - #2138940 - 2139757, April. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - #2140189 - 2140776, April. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - #2140800 - 2141310, April. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - #2141351 - 2141668, April. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - #2141692 - 2141997, April. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - #2142004 - 2142353, April. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - #2142354 - 2143356, April. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - #2143454 - 2143546, May. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - #2143617 - 2145751, May. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - #2145771 - 2146344, May. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - #2146446 - 2146692, May. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - #2146923 - 2148708, May. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - #2148710 - 2149869, May. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - #2149872 - 2150454, May. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - #2150460 - 2151327, May. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - #2151450 - 2153353, May. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - #2153534 - 2154809, May. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - #2155289 - 2155813, May. (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - #2155828 - 2157545, May. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - #2157613 - 2157869, May - June. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - #2157947 - 2159452, June. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - #2159489 - 2160320, June. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - #2160508 - 2161441, June. (Box 73, Folder 5)